(Howard:)The old people just came up
to you, pinched your cheek
(Howard:)and handed you a savings bond.
(Raj:)Oh, don't be such gloomy Gusses.
(Raj:)Look at the size
of these shrimp!
(Raj:)At what point do we start
calling them lobsters?
(Leonard:)Face it, Raj,
we crashed and burned tonight.
(Mrs Latham:)Oh, you didn't
do that badly.
(Leonard:)Mrs. Latham, the first machine
I turn on in the morning
(Leonard:)is the helium-neon laser,
'cause it needs to warm up.
(Mrs Latham:)I no longer care, dear.
(Mrs Latham:)But don't worry,
(Mrs Latham:)I really enjoyed
meeting you this evening.
(Howard:)u're kidding.
That was good for you?
'Cause I was sweating
through my T-shirt.
(Mrs Latham:)Excellent! There's
nothing I like better
(Mrs Latham:)than making smart people
feel ill at ease.
(Leonard:)Why?
(Mrs Latham:)Oh, I don't know,
it's one of the fun things
(Mrs Latham:)you get to do when
you have lots of money.
(Mrs Latham:)Watch.
(Mrs Latham:)Hey! Who said you
could eat that shrimp?
(Mrs Latham:)See? Fun.
(Sheldon(behind them):)No, no, no, I'm just here
(Sheldon(behind them):)for your money.